

JOÃO GARCEZ

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

26 YEARS

I've always been interested in technology and I look at it as a way to solve real world problems. Currently, I work as a fullstack software developer and I have three years of experience. In the future, I pretend to specialize in the frontend area, developing mobile applications or web applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE TECHNOLOGIES

ReactJS

ReactNative

Javascript & Typescript

Nodejs

Nextis

HTML

CSS

Java

Spring

Flutter

Git

SQL

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

REST API & JSON

Oct 2019 - Dec 2021

Jan 2021 - Present

LANGUAGES

Portuguese (Native)

English (Intermediate)

Spanish (Basic)

Aug 2017 - Sep 2017

CONTACTS



+351 912042750



joao10garcez@gmail.com





https://joaogarcez.com



in https://www.linkedin.com/in /joaogarcez/

Cascais, Lisbon - Portugal

Jun 2016 - Jul 2016

Nov 2015 - Jan 2016

Warehouse operator

Go Natural Estoril

Reception and load confirmation; Stock replenishment.

Mobile Seller

Worten CascaisShopping

Monitoring and advising customers in store; Knowledge of market trends, news and releases; Sales.

Application Development Analyst Accenture

Project for a Portuguese public sector organization whose purpose is to administer taxes and customs duties.

Development, maintenance and deployment of various applications, webservices, batch's.

Technologies: Java, Spring, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Oracle Database (PL/SQL), Weblogic Server, Git, SonarQube, SOAP.

Application Development Associate

Accenture

Project for a portuguese corporate group focused essentially on the postal business.

Development and maintenance of CRM platform tailored for the company's employees.

Technologies: Java, Spring, Javascript, HTML, CSS, REST API, Oracle Engament Cloud.



JOÃO GARCEZ

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

26 YEARS

I've always been interested in technology and I look at it as a way to solve real world problems. Currently, I work as a fullstack software developer and I have three years of experience. In the future, I pretend to specialize in the frontend area, developing mobile applications or web applications.

SOFT SKILLS

Organization

Proactivity

Creativity

Critical thinking

Teamwork

Problem solving

CERTIFICATES

The Complete 2021

Flutter Development **Bootcamp with Dart**

VOLUNTEERING EXPERIENCE

Feb 2017 - May 2018 🜳

Image Section Collaborator

AEISCTE-IUL

Editing and creating images and posters.

Technologies: Photoshop.

Jun 2017 - Jul 2017 Jun 2016 - Aug 2016 🔾 Locals

Cascais Town Hall

Provision of tourist services: Railway transport assistance; Organization and management of teams.

May 2016 O

EYE FESTIVAL (European Youth Event), Strasbourg

Oct 2015

ENJ (National Youth Meeting), **Estoril**

Udemy

EDUCATION

2016 - 2019

Computer Engineering

ISCTE-IUL, Lisbon - Degree

2015 - 2016

Computer and Software Engineering

IST - Instituto Superior Técnico - Campus Taguspark, Oeiras (Portugal) - 1.º Year

joao10garcez@gmail.com

CONTACTS

+351 912042750

https://joaogarcez.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in /joaogarcez/

Cascais, Lisbon - Portugal

2011 - 2014

Scientific and Humanistic Science and Technology Course

School Salesianos of Manique, Cascais (Portugal)